chatdd.com 2014-03-29

# ChatDD.Com - Privacy Policy

**_Before using any of our any service & tools, you must read the following terms and conditions._**

The privacy of our visitors to Chatdd.com is important to us. 

At Chatdd.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Chatdd.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**ChatDD Forums Community**  
The opinions expressed within our Discussion Boards are the opinions of the individual poster and not necessarily shared by the forum owner. We reserve the right to remove any messages from the discussion boards at any time for any reason. 

Poster are owner of their content we are not responsible for their postings, if they post anything illegal, Let us know we,ll remove it ASAP. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on Chatdd.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

**.NET Passport Privacy Policy:**   
We do not Save/Log/Record your Passport username or Passport. This information is required to log into your Passport account to perform the tasks provided the Tools at Chatdd.com. If you still feel insecure, we suggest you to temporarily change the password before using any of our tools. 

**Copyright:**   
All content including Text & Images are the property of Chatdd.com. Windows, MSN and MSN Messenger are registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation. AOL and AIM are registered trademarks of America Online, Inc. ICQ is a registered mark of ICQ, Inc. Yahoo is a service mark of Yahoo. THIS SITE IS NOT AFFILIATED IN ANY WAY WITH MICROSOFT CORPORATION, AMERICA ONLINE, ICQ OR YAHOO. 

**Third Party Advertising:**   
We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Third Party Cookies:**   
In the course of serving advertisements, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Disclaimer:**   
We do not take any responsibility for any error or omission by Chatdd.com or Third Parties. We don't request or save any personal information including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. We are not responsible for any damage caused by anyone using our tools or directly by our tools. 

## Latest Threads from ChatDD Forums:

**More Resources  

**
